Hey everyone, thanks for listening to
the Grow Your Life podcast. My name is
Jeremiah Kowski. On this podcast, I help
coaches, mentors, and service providers
scale their businesses by getting more
leads, more customers, and more clients
using direct response marketing,
copywriting, and online paid
advertising. Now, in this episode of
this podcast, we're going to take a
little bit of a different direction. I
want to talk about how you can literally
use one AI prompt to build a business
and you can build software as well using
AI. This is sounds like science fiction,
but this is something that we dreamed
about for years. And I find that some
people sometimes they look back and
they're like, gosh, I wish that I was in
the dot boom during the 2000s. I would
have made so much money. Or I wish I
knew how to code. Or I wish that I had
gotten into Bitcoin when Bitcoin first
started.
AI is that opportunity right now and a
lot of people are still sleeping on it.
A lot of you right now who are listening
to this still don't even have a chat GPT
account. And I find that fascinating.
Maybe because you're afraid of AI taking
over your job or or you think that it's
not personal enough. But can I tell you
AI goes so much deeper than that.
Artificial intelligence is a tool that
you can use to build with. It's
intelligent. It creates different things
in different realms and it's a
worldbuilder is what it is. And so what
you get to do with artificial
intelligence goes far beyond just simply
oh I want to write some sales copy or I
want to write some emails. We've talked
about that ad nauseium on this podcast.
I can't talk about it much more to be
honest. The processes are there. You can
go through the episodes on all the
different ways you can use AI for
marketing. But the things that I think
most people don't know that you can do
is it can do research for you. It can
come up with new uh they just found that
it came up with new math even. Now that
doesn't affect you necessarily or what
you're trying to accomplish. But let me
explain this to you, okay? Is it's
almost like having an intern that works
for you that's extremely intelligent.
The problem is is the intern
is not as skilled with doing stuff in
the world that you're in. And so you
have to guide and direct it. And that's
really the difference with AI is that AI
lacks skill and experience that we as
human beings have. And so we're guiding,
directing, and steering it in the
directions that we want. But what it is
is it's actually extremely intelligent.
It's actually a PhD level of
intelligence now that can accomplish
incredible things. And so you can use it
to help you process through tough
problems. You can have it identify
patterns. Um, but it can also take an
idea that you have and help you massage
it and create it. And so I want to just
show you just a few different
applications. If you're on the uh
YouTube version of this podcast, you can
actually see my screen that I'm going to
be sharing here on screen to kind of
walk you through this. But I'm going to
explain everything that's on screen as
well for those of you who are just
listening. So, a couple of different
apps that are out there. One of the most
um advanced ones is called Cursor. And
this one is like it it uses AI to write
code. If you've ever been like, I want
to learn to write code. The thing about
cursor is you have to still kind of
understand how to do code. So, for most
people, it's probably a little bit too
advanced. There's a couple of other
great tools that are out there. One of
them is called Lovable.
Lovable, it's not lovable. Lovable.
You look up lovable, lovable.dev. Okay.
And what Lovable is is it is an
application that allows you to build
websites and go based on templates and
create tools. So they give you these
prototyping templates that you can go
based off of. And then you could
actually build out dashboards or
different functions or tools using this
with one simple prompt like this. create
me a dashboard where people can let me
let me actually log into my account here
if I have a have a chance to
I'll show you this because I actually
have a paid account with mobile
premium dashboard where people can
schedule service providers who come to
pick up their junk outside of their
home.
Okay. And so right here, Lovable is
going to create a dashboard using the
artificial intelligence to be able to do
this. It's going to create a preview of
everything that we're doing on that
process. Now, we're going to come back
to this. Uh, it's going to take some
time to do this. We're going to come
back to it. I want to show you some of
the other different types of tools that
there are. See, it's already processing.
Okay, here's what I'm going to create.
Here's what I'm going to put together.
The AI has an intelligent agent that
actually does this. A couple of other
tools that are out there. Replet. Replet
very similar, but it has a full server
stack back end of it where this is where
you can actually host your server and do
all of that type of technical stuff. And
it's one of the easiest to use to get up
and running with an actual front-end
site. One of the things that I do is I
could actually move something from
lovable over to Replet over here. And it
has the AI agent. There's different
resources, community examples, uh,
inspiration gallery right here that you
can actually go through and you can find
different apps that other people have
created. And you can even, uh, a lot of
these you can view them, you can clone
them, you can do different things like
that. Okay. There's another app that's
out there called bolt.new.
I have an account with bolt.new as well
um, that does this very similar to
Replet that creates the whole server top
to bottom. And a lot of these
applications only run you about $25 a
month for unlimited levels of being able
to do this type of stuff. Reflet right
here is going to run you right around
$20 a month. Uh lovable.dev
is going to run you around, let's see,
$50 a month. So again, I have a pro plan
right here that I actually got for for
free from a promotion that I get to use.
Um it's a whole year that I actually got
which is awesome. And so the idea is
with doing this
with with lovable with Replet with bolt
new is that you can prototype any idea
that you have for an application for
functionality for something that even
doesn't exist right now. to take a
vision, to take an idea that you have
and to put it together that you can use
to create a business around. You don't
need to know how to code. You don't need
to know how to um put all the pieces
together. You can literally just prompt
it. And then what it does is it has a
simple screen like chat GPT that you can
chat with right here. See, look, this
has let me let me move my screen over to
the corner right here.
This has a prompt right here where you
can ask it questions. You can edit
certain things. You can edit certain
files, documents, ask for different
types of knowledge, and things like that
for it to accomplish what you're looking
for. So, right here,
uh, Lovable is going to show us what it
just created. It just went ahead and
created a prototype based on one simple
prompt right here. Create me a dashboard
where people can schedule this. Right
here you can enter your location.
Let's enter our location. Right here you
can select a service
search. Okay. Now this is just a
front-end dashboard. This has a whole
thing where it has uh available service
providers that you can book. It has all
these different things like this. So we
didn't give it much details.
But what it's doing is it's actually
going ahead and it's creating that
prototypical
front end for us for how to do this. So
what this did was it's actually found us
some people in our area that it could do
that could do this. So we can book this
person for this week for this type of
service. Uh let's see 810 Belmont Drive,
Austin, Texas.
Okay, confirm booking. And you can
literally see how in one instance this
did this. Now, this might not be exactly
what I'm wanting. Um, I already have a
front end. I just want to schedule this
in a roundroin system where uh it will
link it to my private backend crew.
Okay. So, for instance, I can adjust, I
can modify it, I can give it that app
where it says I already have the front
end. So, it's going to go to work and
it's going to process through changing
this to being able to do this. And this
is just two prompts that we've been able
to do to have even a working prototype
of something that we could then build
and expand into. And this is the beauty
and this is the amazing thing that
running and using artificial
intelligence like this allows us to do
is that you can do this. And then here's
the other thing that you can do. You can
then take an application like this
and you can create your marketing in
chat GPT. ChatGBT just released their
GPT5
version of the application and it is
extremely intelligent with creating
marketing. So, if I take this right
here, if I just take the front end that
that Lovable created about this junk
removal service, I could say, "Generate
me all the marketing materials I need to
get clients for this service
business." And it can start to
brainstorm this with you. I think this
is where a lot of people, they're like,
"Oh, I don't know what to do for
marketing. I don't know what to do in my
business to be able to get clients or to
be able to make stuff work for me." when
in fact artificial intelligence
literally can give you the answers just
by simply asking it questions. It can
create a marketing kit for you. It can
create ideas, USPs, ad copy, landing
pages, social media assets to get you
started right here. It's even going to
work like this one right here. It's
identifying the neighborhood
neighborhoods like Avery Ranch and Cedar
Park. by the way, like I used to I used
to live there. So that's why it's
literally pulling the zip codes and it's
knowing how to uh utilize those that
different detail right there in this and
it's creating these marketing material
and ideas as well as plans that you can
come up with. Okay, great. Here's a
marketing kit for this.
Okay,
phone script chatbot. This is amazing.
Operation SOPs,
brand and positioning,
value pillars, target segments,
irresistible offers, same day
residential,
contractor advantage program, HOA, bulk
pickup, price match guarantee,
pricing framework, how to price things
out.
Okay.
high converting landing page ideas.
It's uh it's even it's it's trying to
generate us a like a front-end uh
landing page and things like that. Let's
go in and let's stop this. Let's say
generate me just some social media post
ideas to get attention.
Okay.
And see what this creates.
I find that so often people are using AI
the wrong way because they're just
relying on the first prompt that it
gives them rather than asking it to do
different ideas or questions or things
like that. So for instance, right here,
what does a quarter truck really look
like? Same day timer. from a countdown
from booking to driveway to pickup.
Guess the price. Show a pile. Ask
followers to come up with estimates.
Will it fit?
Different ideas of will it fit? Truth.
Two truths and a junk lie. Mythbusting.
All junk goes to the landfill. What
contractors wish homeowners knew. Okay.
Local community angles. Uh HOA bulk day
invite.
Uh polls, quizzes, authority posts. How
do we price things? Offers that pop, UGC
ideas.
And so again, when it comes to your
marketing,
when it comes to doing this,
it is not
difficult
for you to be able to create from idea
to product to output.
to get the results that you want. As a
business owner, as somebody who has
ideas in business, as somebody who
solves problems, you can take the ideas
that are in your mind and have AI create
you a prototype, you can have AI help
you come up with marketing ideas, and
then you can test things out. Now,
here's the problem where I see people
get stuck. They're waiting for all the
details to be perfect to launch
something. They're waiting for all the
details to be defined and refined before
they put something out there. And I'm
telling you, my friends, this is
just
a losing battle for you. This is just
completely
not the direction that you want to go
in. You need to become a person who has
the ability to test and iterate your
ideas, who can get out of your own way
instead of waiting for the perfect
scenarios or the perfect setup or the
perfect ideas.
You're willing to take a risk, put
yourself out there just to see what
happens, just to see how things happen.
just to see
is it going to work? Is there a market
for this? What kind of response do I
get? So often I see business owners,
potential business owners
missing it because they are creating
from a place of I need it to be perfect.
I need to have everything figured out
first. I need to have all the details
figured out before I get started.
And this is preventing people
from seeing the kind of results,
having their dreams come together
because they're going to be sitting on
potential ideas without
prototyping to see is it going to work?
Can it work? Can this get me a result? I
promise you, my friends,
this will get you a result. If you go
out there, if you test things out, if
you're willing to try stuff out just to
see what happens,
you could create software, you could
create websites, you could create entire
businesses from scratch. You could even
do this as a service for other
businesses. You can market what I just
showed you in this video in the last 15
minutes as a service to other business
owners.
Some of these tools that I've shown you,
Replet, Bolt, new, lovable, even cursor,
which is the higherend coding version of
all this, are some of the greatest
opportunities that we have in front of
us right now to be able to create and
build and accomplish the dreams and
goals that we have.
We need to get out of our own way,
myself included. I talk about this
myself to myself. I need to get out of
my own way. You need to get out of your
own way. We all are our greatest worst
enemy when it comes to creating and
building the kind of things that we want
because we're letting the need for it to
be perfect, for it to work out. The the
the fear of wasted time or things not
working out, letting the worry and the
fear of what if it doesn't go how I want
it to stop you from taking action. And
I'm telling you, if you keep doing that,
you are going to struggle and struggle
and struggle.
And so I, you know, I'm sorry,
but artificial intelligence is one of
the greatest opportunities that are out
there for you to accomplish the things
that you want to accomplish.
And
you need to start to learn how to use
these tools and you need to start
implementing them and stop letting your
pride and your ego keep you from going
out there to do these types of things.
You can see we created it created this
backend crew management dashboard. It
shows this right here different you can
create different assignments once
somebody's booked and things like that.
So, it's already going ahead and it's
already creating these types of things
and it's telling you what to do, what
needs to happen, what needs to be
adjusted to be able to create this.
We live in one of the greatest times of
opportunity that has ever existed when
it comes to building and creating
businesses.
The only reason why most people don't
have a business they want is they're
afraid of it not working out and they're
work waiting for the perfect setup or
the perfect moment or the perfect
opportunity. Stop waiting for perfect.
Start getting results. That's why I
built my Wealthy Coach Academy program.
My Wealthy Coach Academy program is
where I work with business owners every
single week to become wealthy to take
their ideas, how do I market it, how do
I create advertising campaigns, how do I
create the social media content that
gets results, how do I create the things
that are going to move the needle
forward in my business? And so, if you
want to jump into that program, again,
check out one of the links below. You
can watch one of the free classes that I
have and there's always going to be an
opportunity for you to jump in to work
with me inside of one of those. That's
the way to come in. That's the way to
work with me. That's the way to get
results. Grow your life everybody. We'll
talk soon.
[Music]
[Applause]